LAURA DIAZ

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



My portfolio



lauradiaz1586@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I'm a Frontend Developer with two years of experience in blending the art of design with the skill of programming to deliver an immersive and engaging user experience through efficient website development and proactive feature optimization.

EXPERIENCE

06/2021 - Present

Dorothy - Frontend Developer

Frontend development of different company products. I identify and fix bugs/technical issues before and after deploying. Depending on the project needs, I implemented Redux and Context API for state management.

Tech stack: NextJs (ReactJs Framework), Redux.

06/2020 - 05/2021

Freelance - Frontend Developer

A freelance project for a Graphic and Typeface designer is a responsive website built in NextJs. I worked closely with the designer. https://ferminguerrero.com/. **Tech stack:** Next Js (React Js Framework).

05/2016 - 06/2020

Emirates Airline - Cabin Crew

12/2014 - 04/2016

Telefonica - Workforce Management Analyst

Analyzed, controlled, and managed the services in the Customer Service Department. Executed actions and launched the contingency plan for any situation that may impact Customer Service performance.

12/2014 - 04/2016

Directy - Workforce Management Analyst

My work consisted of controlling in realtime the behavior of the Customer Service Center's traffic calls. Ensured compliance with a high service level. Created reports about customer service agent's performance. I Solved problems that affected the business.

04/2010 - 04/2013

Directy - Customer Service Agent

Customer Care Support.

06/2009 - 03/2010

Big Ben Institute - Administrative

Administrative tasks.

EDUCATION

2020

Frontend Development Coding Bootcamp

Frontend development coding bootcamp with an extension of +200 hours.
Skills: HTML5, CSS, Javascript (ES6),
ReactJs.